newwpthemes.net 2013-01-15

# Privacy Policy

##  [Privacy Policy](http://newwpthemes.net/privacy-policy/ "Permalink to Privacy Policy")

Privacy Policy for NewWPThemes.net

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at contact @ newwpthemes.net.

At NewWPThemes.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by NewWPThemes.net and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, NewWPThemes.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

NewWPThemes.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include, but are not limited to: Google Adsense, Commission Junction, Linkshare, Adbrite, DoubleClick and other third-party ad servers to serve and display advertisements on NewWPThemes.net.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on NewWPThemes.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) You can get further information regarding the DART cookie at [Doubleclick](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx).

For more information about these third-party ad networks and opting out of tracking, please visit:

  * <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>
  * <http://networkadvertising.org/managing>

NewWPThemes.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. NewWPThemes.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

A useful resource on understanding Cookies may be found at [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

**Changes**

As the standards governing Internet privacy continue to evolve, NewWPThemes.net may find it appropriate or necessary to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. As a result, we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and shall post such changes on the Website. Our Website will state the date the Privacy Policy was last updated. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you use this Website to make sure you understand how your information will be used.

It is possible that portions or all of  NewWPThemes.net may be sold to another company. In that event, applicable user information whether personally identifiable or otherwise may be transferred as part of that sale.

_Last updated 10/21/09_

views:
    33
keyword_cache:
    a:1:{s:13:"keywords_time";i:1226319523;}
title_tag:
    NewWPThemes | New Wordpress Themes Privacy Policy
